As someone who's been in City Hall since I was 23, I tell the younger elected officials now,
when your name no longer has a title on it, these folks are not going to answer your phone call.
But those people standing on that street corner who have known you your whole life,
they're going to answer you. And you have to be able to, when you're done with,
don't let this position consume who you are. You're there for a reason. You're there to work
for the people. You're there to accomplish everything you can accomplish when you're there.
You know, I infamously say all the time, you have to do the right thing, not the popular one,
even if it hurts your election, even if it hurts your politics, right? And that's a scary thing
for some people because they can't see past their life in their current role. Like I said,
after our first one, like if they come and get me four years, eight years, whatever, oh well,
I've been able to done so much that they'll never be able to undo in that time. And that's what really
matters.